<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Carbon Tracker</string>
    <string name="view_carbon_footprint">View Carbon FootPrint</string>
    <string name="create_a_new_journey">Create a New Journey</string>
    <string name="add_a_new_journey">Add a New Journey</string>
    <string name="save_route">Save Route</string>
    <string name="edit_route">Edit</string>
    <string name="delete_route">Delete</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="add_a_new_car">Add a New Car</string>
    <string name="nick_name">Nick Name:</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="year">Year</string>
    <string name="model">Model</string>
    <string name="make">Make</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="nickname">NickName:</string>
    <string name="distance">Distance</string>
    <string name="nick_name_for_route">Nick Name for Route</string>
    <string name="city_distance_in_km">City Distance in KM</string>
    <string name="high_way_distance_in_km">Highway Distance in KM</string>
    <string name="highway_km">Highway (km):</string>
    <string name="city_km">City (km):</string>
    <string name="switch_view">Switch View</string>
    <string name="nickname_for_car">Nickname for Car</string>
    <string name="km_driven_in_city">KM Driven in City:</string>
    <string name="km_driven_on_highway">KM Driven on Highway:</string>
    <string name="route_name">Route Name:</string>
    <string name="context_edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="add_a_new_route">Add a New Route</string>
    <string name="context_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="add_route">Add Route</string>
    <string name="error_toast">Please name your car before adding it to your collection</string>
    <string name="btn_splash_start">start</string>
    <string name="App_name">Carbon Tracker</string>
    <string name="authors_text">Authors: Team Honeydew</string>
    <string-array name="menu">
        <item>Edit</item>
        <item>Delete</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="next_tip">Next Tip</string>
    <string name="close_tips">Close</string>
    <string-array name="tips_array">
        <item>Carpool with commuters that share similar trips to yours.</item>
        <item>If looking to get a new car, take into consideration fuel efficiency when choosing which vehicle to get.</item>
        <item>If possible, take a bus instead of a taxi or other forms of single-passenger transportation.</item>
        <item>Try to prevent stopping and accelerating as much as you can when driving.</item>
        <item>If in traffic, turn off your engine if idling for long periods of time.</item>
        <item>Try to take the most direct path to your destination to avoid taking detours that will add to your trip length.</item>
        <item>If going short distances, consider walking, biking, or other forms of zero-emission transportation.</item>
        <item>Make sure your wheels are fully inflated, as flatter tires greatly increase your emissions.</item>
        <item>Taking shorter showers can help greatly reduce the amount of hot water you consume, which will reduce your carbon footprint.</item>
        <item>Washing clothes in cold water will reduce the amount of unnecessary hot water you use.</item>
        <item>Turning off heating in the warmer months will drastically decrease the amount of gas used for heating.</item>
        <item>Put a sweatshirt on instead of turning up the heat when cold.</item>
        <item>Using compact fluorescent light bulbs will cut down on your electric bill and also increase the brightness of the rooms you're trying to light!</item>
        <item>Unplugging electrical appliances that aren't in use will reduce the amount of ambient electricity you use.</item>
        <item>During the warmer months, hang your clothes up to dry instead of using a drying machine to cut down on your electric bill.</item>
        <item>If going on vacation, turn off the heating in your house and put your water heater on "vacation" setting if possible.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>